geckotribe.com 2017-06-11

# Gecko Tribe, LLC Privacy & Content Policies

_Last Updated: Jan 28, 2016_

## Personal Information

We track visitor activity on our websites, and in some place, collect personal information as needed to provide and improve our sites, and to facilitate communication with and between members. By using the site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

No personally identifiable information that we collect will ever be disclosed (other than as aggregates like totals, averages, etc. which are not personally identifiable) to any third party without your explicit approval, except as described in this policy, unless required by law.

## Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this data.

## Cookies  

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. When you load subsequent pages from the same website, your browser sends the same information back to the server from which it came.

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

We use cookies to enabling signing in, to improve your experience on our sites, and to help us analyze how individuals are using the site. No cookies that we place contain personal data.

Cookies may also be placed by other services (such as Google Analytics) that are used on our sites.

## Profile Information

On the profile editing page, we collect information that may be displayed on public profile pages on our sites. The privacy level for each piece of information (eg. public, visible only to signed-in members, visible only to site administrators) is clearly indicated on the editing screen, and you may control the privacy level for some items. Email addresses are always kept private.

You may edit or remove this information or your privacy settings at any time. Changes that you make will be reflected immediately.

## Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of  
transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Analytics Tools

We use analytics tools and other third party technologies, such as Google Analytics and DoubleClick Cookies, to collect non-personal information in the form of various usage and user metrics when you use our online Sites and/or Services. These tools and technologies collect and analyze certain types of information, including cookies, IP addresses, device and software identifiers, referring and exit URLs, onsite behavior and usage information, feature use metrics and statistics, usage and purchase history, MAC Address, mobile unique device ID, and other similar information.

The third party analytics companies who collect information on our Sites and/or Services and other online products and/or services may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other websites and/or other online or mobile products and services relating to your activities across their network of websites as well as online and/or mobile products and services. Many of these companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies.

In addition to our use of technologies as described herein, we may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to you based on your use of our sites and/or services and to otherwise collect and use data about your use of our sites and/or services. For more information about this practice, please see the “Third Party Advertising Technologies” section below.

[How to opt out of Google advertising](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads). [How to opt out of Google Analytics](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). [How to opt out of Facebook tracking](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217).

Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746), and Restrictions.

You may view a list of other third party service providers who collect information, and/or opt-out of such collection of information about you, by visiting <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>.

## Third Party Advertising Technologies

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products or placing advertisements, these third party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on any of our Sites and/or Services and on third party websites. Each of these companies uses this cookie information according to their own privacy and security policies. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out as indicated in this Policy. Please note this does not opt you out of being delivered advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

## Children Under 13

We do not knowingly seek or collect Personal Information from users under the age of 13. Users under 13 years of age, your continued use of the Site and/or Service will be considered by us as confirmation that your parent or guardian has expressly consented to the handling of your Personal Information as described in this Policy.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date displayed above, and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

Gecko Tribe, LLC  
PO Box 5835  
Grand Island, NE 68802  
Voice Mail: 308-646-0543
